Hey Gabe, hope you're having a great Monday and you had a good weekend.
We're just about done with the discovery, and so I just wanted to take
a minute to kind of go through all of the items and documents that
we have here for you. Came and I'll be getting with you later to
schedule some time. Awesome, so at the root of the repo you're going to
find, just like a master migration document.
That way you've kind of got all of the data that you'll need,
or will need as we go through. This is very extensive,
it goes over every repository that you have,
all the scopes, basically everything that,
that was given to me by Faraway, just to make sure that everything's covered,
complete breakdown of your application stack and how that's going to be migrated into
AWS. We've also got this GitHub repo.
This is just a shallow clone. In here is this infrastructure analysis from GitHub,
where I just kind of go over, all the bits and bobs from HeavyMetal.
And then in here is a shallow clone of all of your repos.
If you'd like, we can get these transferred over to your GitHub.
some of these repos have a lot of your game assets and stuff.
So they're super big. So I don't have all of them in here, especially
the other side mono repo. but once we get started,
I can go ahead and get those migrated all the way into your GitHub.
Other things you'll see in here is the CloudFlare migration intake.
This is a complete and entire extensive, like migration workflow that I set up
for you. That just kind of goes over literally every single,
HeavyMetal.com or HeavyMetal, domain that we have, all of the objects that kind of
go into this and
like what it's going to take to get that taken care of for you.
There's also like, code snippets that I turned into actual code that was just
provided for me via the screenshots, which are also here,
that can be came from far away.
there's also resources here. This is just like another CSV of everything that's inside
of your current product.
And so with that, that'll conclude the CloudFlare.
And then we also have AWS. So AWS has just a few things in
here. There's a pre-transfer checklist. Just, we're just going to go through to make
sure that you have everything that you need before we take that AWS account.
There's an inventory checklist, scripting that we use to kind of intake all of
the objects inside of AWS, so that when we transfer it,
we can confirm that everything made it over. That way,
if anything gets missed, we can take care of that for you.
And then there's a cutover plan from the moment that it gets cut over
from fairway to it being in your hands and everything that we'll do to
kind of make sure that everything's sorted for you. Awesome.
Well, I hope you're having a great day. And then the last one is
just the big migration document. Hope you're having a great day.
Hope you're ready for the holidays. And we'll talk soon.
Bye.